<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://theme336-tile-stone.myshopify.com/blogs/blog.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme336-tile-stone.myshopify.com/blogs/blog"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://theme336-tile-stone.myshopify.com/blogs/blog/tagged/wood-look.atom"/>
  <title>DStone - Blog</title>
  <updated>2017-05-30T11:54:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>DStone</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://theme336-tile-stone.myshopify.com/blogs/blog/aesthetic-component-is-so-high-that-you-can-create-truly-royal-interiors</id>
    <published>2017-05-30T11:54:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-06-06T10:13:07-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme336-tile-stone.myshopify.com/blogs/blog/aesthetic-component-is-so-high-that-you-can-create-truly-royal-interiors"/>
    <title>Aesthetic component is so high that you can create truly royal interiors</title>
    <author>
      <name>David Braun</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[So as you see, tile and stone are universal finishing materials, which allow you to implement any design ideas you have and at the same time save your efforts &amp; money. They will serve you for decades, delighting you with their brilliance and sophisticated design.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://theme336-tile-stone.myshopify.com/blogs/blog/aesthetic-component-is-so-high-that-you-can-create-truly-royal-interiors">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">So as you see, tile and stone are universal finishing materials, which allow you to implement any design ideas you have and at the same time save your efforts &amp; money. They will serve you for decades, delighting you with their brilliance and sophisticated design. Whether you <strong>need a ceramic tile, glass tile or natural stone</strong> for your interior, feel free to contact our online store representative and we will gladly help you find the right material for your design! That's why finishing of the interiors and outdoor facades is often performed with the help of exactly these materials that can globally change the entire apartment look.</p>
<p>They will serve you for decades, delighting you with their brilliance and sophisticated design. Whether you need a ceramic tile, glass tile or natural stone for your interior, feel free to contact our online store representative and we will gladly help you find the right material for your design!</p>
<p>Going to make repairs in your house, apartment or office soon? Or you just want to "refresh" the interior and make the room more stylish and elegant? Or maybe you want to add a new element in some room for the perception of the antique? Our online store has a wide range of tile and stone that can be used for the arrangement of any premises. Whatever modern and innovative materials appear on the market of finishing materials, tiles and stone still are in the priority.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
